windycitynovelties.com 2019-01-27

# Privacy Policy

The contents of the Windy City Novelties web site are provided as general information only. In no event will Windy City Novelties or the contributors of information to this site be liable to you or anyone else for any action taken by you in reliance on such information or for any consequential, special, or similar damages. The following discloses Windy City Novelties practices for protecting the privacy of visitors to our web site, [www.windycitynovelties.com](https://www.windycitynovelties.com/)

**Access to All Sections of the Web Site Without Providing Personal Information**

Visitors can access all sections of the web site without providing any personal, identifying information.

**Voluntary Use of Contact Forms**

Windy City Novelties Forms are where visitors may voluntarily provide personal information, including name, company/organization, city and state of residence, and telephone numbers. The contact information is only used to contact the visitor as requested. Windy City Novelties does NOT collect personally identifiable contact information, and does NOT distribute to third parties any information provided on Windy City Novelties Forms. We will not disclose under any circumstances an individual's/employee's identifying information provided by voluntary use of a Contact Form, or specific use of the system to any individual, employer, or organization. Further, only a group of trained and authorized employees has access to information you volunteer via a Contact Form and they along with all our employees must abide by our privacy policy. Those who violate our privacy policy are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

**Helpful Links**

Our site contains links to other sites. These links are provided for your convenience and are not intended as an endorsement by Windy City Novelties of the organizations operating these sites nor as a warranty of the information they contain. Windy City Novelties is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other web sites, and urge users to review privacy policies. Again, visitors always can accept or reject any cookies from our web sites by taking advantage of the related settings and tools on their own computers.

**Third Party Services**

We use third-party service providers to provide product recommendations and enhance your shopping experience on our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this Web site in order to provide personalized recommendations and advertisements about our goods and services on our Web site as well as when you visit other Web sites.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

**Email Addresses**

We do not rent, share, or exchange our customers' email addresses (except as described in the paragraph below), but we do use these addresses for our own promotional email marketing. You may opt out of receiving promotional emails anytime. Instructions on how to opt out are included in every promotional email, or you may opt out [here](https://windycitynovelties.us17.list-manage.com/unsubscribe/post).

**Sharing Information**

Except as noted above, we may share information about our customers in a variety of ways. We share customer information among the businesses affiliated with Windy City Novelties. We may share customer information with merchants whose websites link with ours. We may also employ other businesses or consultants to perform functions such as sending mail or e-mail, analyzing data and customer lists, processing accounts receivable, marketing or other functions. In those situations, third parties will have access to customer information for the purpose of performing their functions. Though we do not rent, share or exchange customer email addresses in the ordinary course of business, we may sell, transfer or assign customer information in connection with a merger, consolidation, sale of assets or similar business transaction. You may opt-out from our stored database at anytime [here](https://windycitynovelties.us17.list-manage.com/unsubscribe/post).

**Contacting Windy City Novelties Regarding This Privacy Policy**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our site, or your dealings with our web site, please contact:

Web Site Manager  
[ Windy City Novelties  
300 Lakeview Parkway  
Vernon Hills, IL 60061](https://www.google.com/maps/place/Windy+City+Novelties,+Inc./@42.231474,-87.9483313,18z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x880f96113f511d5f:0x6f1377435a38cf81!8m2!3d42.231474!4d-87.947237?hl=en-En)  
Telephone: [800.442.9722](tel:8004429722)
